Step 1: click (915, 175) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center of the page. The search box is located in the header
Step 2: click (897, 175) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The search box is visible with placeholder text 'Sea
Step 3: click (895, 175) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center of the page. The search bo
Step 4: click (895, 175) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center of the page. The search box is located at approximate
Step 5: click (895, 175) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The previous attempts have been clicking at coordina
Step 6: click (897, 175) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center of the page. The previous attempts to click at coordi
Step 7: find_and_click (1189, 190) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center of the page. The previous attempts have been clicking
Step 8: type  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The previous actions show
Step 9: key  [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The task history shows th
Step 10: click (1212, 175) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage. The task history shows that I've already typed 'screenpilot d
Step 11: click (915, 175) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The task history shows mu
Step 12: click (897, 175) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center of the page. The task hist
Step 13: find_and_click (1176, 189) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The task history shows mu
Step 14: click (897, 175) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The search box appears to
Step 15: click (895, 175) [OK]\NI can see the YouTube homepage with a search box at the top center. The search box has placeholder text 'Search' and is